Audio Library:

NAudio 1.5 Build Sun Dec 18 2011 by Mark Heath

NAudio is an open source .NET audio and MIDI library, containing dozens of useful audio related classes intended to speed development of audio related utilities in .NET. It has been in development since 2002 and has grown to include a wide variety of features. While some parts of the library are relatively new and incomplete, the more mature features have undergone extensive testing and can be quickly used to add audio capabilities to an existing .NET application.

Official Website:
http://naudio.codeplex.com/

Themes:

Reuxables Legacy Free Themes Copyright © 1998-2010 Nukeation Studios. All rights reserved.

The Legacy Collection includes popular classic themes such as Candy, Edge, Frog, Inc, Metal, and Sleek along with Mercury, a lightweight version of the new flagship theme Gemini.

Official Website:
http://www.nukeation.com/free.aspx 

WPF Toolkit:

Extended WPF Toolkit 1.7.0 by Xceed

The Extended WPF Toolkit is a collection of WPF controls, components and utilities made available outside the normal WPF Toolkit. Everything is provided with source code and under the Microsoft Public License, so using this toolkit is as friction-free as possible for personal or enterprise use.

Official Website:
http://wpftoolkit.codeplex.com/

People:

Thank to all people who help me to develop this software. Below are the websites:

http://stackoverflow.com/
http://naudio.codeplex.com/discussions

Also thank to my friends for support to this software.

Beathong
Mostan